nvmexpress.org 2014-12-20

# NVM Express » NMV Express Online Privacy Policy

NVM Express respects your privacy choices. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy. The only personal information you will be asked to provide will be your name, company, title, address and e-mail address.

NVM Express encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all web sites you visit. Below is a statement of NVM Express online privacy policy.

### Types and Uses of Personal Information

Your personal information is used in the following ways:

  *  E-mail Correspondence. Used to raise and respond to issues and inquiries of all types. Also used to distribute information about NVM Express and information from Members of NVM Express about their NVM Express related products or events.
  * Direct Member Mailings. Used to distribute NVM Express newsletters and Membership materials as well as for registration at NVM Express events.

We will not change the way in which we use your personal information without your consent.

### Security

We will not collect personal information from you other than what you supply us on a voluntary basis. NVM Express stores no information about the visitors to its web site except for information regarding the manner in which the site is used. Information regarding the manner in which the web site is used will be used only to improve the web site and the content quality and will not display or make available personally identifiable information that is not publicly available.

We protect the personal information you share with us. Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job. We will not disclose your personal information to any third party without receiving your permission.

### Linked Web Sites

We provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control these web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites. NVM Express is not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites and cannot be held liable for any use of private data that they may create.

### Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems.

### Accessing and Updating Information

We need your help in making sure your personal information is correct in our systems. Please notify us of changes to your name, address, title, phone number or email address.

### Unsubscribing

Each email newsletter has instructions on how to unsubscribe.

### Policy updates

All updates to this policy will be posted here.

If you have questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your experience with this web site, please feel free to contact us.
